goldarena.net 2013-09-25

# GoldArena.net - Privacy Policy

GOLDARENA.NET  
PRIVACY POLICY

WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

THIS POLICY COVERS HOW GOLDARENA.NET ("GA") TREATS PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT GA COLLECTS AND RECEIVES. PERSONAL INFORMATION IS INFORMATION ABOUT YOU THAT IS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE LIKE YOUR NAME, ADDRESS, EMAIL ADDRESS OR PHONE NUMBER AND THAT IS NOT OTHERWISE PUBLICLY AVAILABLE.

THIS POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO THE PRACTICES OF COMPANIES THAT GA DOES NOT OWN OR CONTROL OR TO PEOPLE THAT CIN DOES NOT EMPLOY OR MANAGE.

1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Currently, GA only collects personal information when you signup to receive our newsletter.

When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address.

Once you register with us, you are not anonymous to us.

GA automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address and the page you request.

2\. CHILDREN

Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from signing up to any part of the GA web site, this includes registering to receive newsletters.

3\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

GA does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

a. although not at this moment in time, we may in the future provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with GA under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help GA communicate with you about offers from GA and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information;

b. we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

c. we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of GA's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

d. we transfer information about you if GA is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, GA will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

3\. COOKIES

Currently, GA do not create, retrieve or store cookies on your computer.

4\. ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE ACCOUNT INFORMATION

When you signup to receive the GA newsletter, you are opting in to receive information from us. You may decide to opt out at any time by emailing goldarena "@" gmail.com stating that you would like to be removed from any future mailings.

5\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

6\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy with or without informing you.
